{
    "questions": [{
    "problem": "Simplification of (a² - 4b²)⁄((a²+2ab)⁄ab) yields",

    "choice1": "b(a - 2b)",
    "choice2": "a(b - 2a)",
    "choice3": "a + 2b",
    "choice4": "a - 2b",
    "correctanswer": "1"
},
{
    "problem": "Simplifying the expression (m²cx + mc)⁄(m²x² + 2mx + 1) gives us",

    "choice1": "mc⁄(mx + 1)",
    "choice2": "(mx + 1)⁄mc",
    "choice3": "mc + 1⁄m",
    "choice4": "none of above",
    "correctanswer": "1"
},
{
    "problem": "Simplifying the expression (3⁄10)(35⁄54)/(14⁄15) gives",

    "choice1": "24⁄5",
    "choice2": "35⁄6",
    "choice3": "5⁄24",
    "choice4": "6⁄24",
    "correctanswer": "3"
},
{
    "problem": "Evaluate the expression for the given value of the variable: t ÷ 7, t = 42",

    "choice1": "4",
    "choice2": "5",
    "choice3": "6",
    "choice4": "7",
    "correctanswer": "3"
},
{
    "problem": "What is the product of (x+a) and (x+b)?",

    "choice1": " x2+ (a-b)x + ab",
    "choice2": "x2 + (a+b)x - ab",
    "choice3": "x2 + (a+b)x - ab",
    "choice4": "x2 + (a+b)x + ab",
    "correctanswer": "1"
},
{
    "problem": "Evaluate the expression for the given value of the variable: s × 7, s = 5",

    "choice1": "20",
    "choice2": "25",
    "choice3": "30",
    "choice4": "35",
    "correctanswer": "4"
},
{
    "problem": "The product of 4mn and 0 is",

    "choice1": "0",
    "choice2": "1",
    "choice3": "mn",
    "choice4": "4mn",
    "correctanswer": "1"
},
{
    "problem": "The product of 5x and 2y is",

    "choice1": "xy",
    "choice2": "2xy",
    "choice3": "5ay",
    "choice4": "10ay",
    "correctanswer": "4"
},
{
    "problem": "The product of 7x and -12x is",

    "choice1": "84x²",
    "choice2": "-84x²",
    "choice3": " x²",
    "choice4": "-x²",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},
{
    "problem": "The product of x², – x³, – x4 is",

    "choice1": "x9",
    "choice2": "x5",
    "choice3": "x7",
    "choice4": "x6",
    "correctanswer": "1"
}]}